Alp Niksarli

+90 (553) 017 44 44 alp.niksarli@gmail.com

11th grade Robert College student interested in developing products and doing research on computer science and data science related topics. I like to share my coding experience and knowledge voluntarily to provide underserved students an equal opportunity.



Experience

11/2020 to Present

Freelance Python Developer

FIVERR, Istanbul

- Sold services such as data science, machine learning, web/app development and Python scripts.
- Worked with over 50 clients from all around the world.
- Completed all my orders successfully with satisfied clients who left 5-star reviews.
- Here is my profile: https://www.fiverr.com/alpnix

08/2021 to 03/2022

Artificial Intelligence Intern MAGFI, Istanbul

- Developed a natural language processing algorithm that is used by 50k+ users.
- Learned more about database system, specifically, Elasticsearch.

Clubs/Teams

- Besiktas Table Tennis Team
- RC Google Developer Student Club
- RC Makers
- RC Web Development Club
- Data Structures & Algorithms
- RC Artificial Intelligence Club

Highlights

- Team working and leadership
- Risk taking
- Entrepreneurship
- Operability and commitment
- Researching

Education

High School Diploma: Robert College 2018-2023(expected) Istanbul, Turkey

Certifications

- Scientific Computing with Python
- Neural Networks and Deep Learning
- Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization
- Python and TensorFlow for Data Science